designyoutrust.com 2014-05-16

# Privacy » Design You Trust

## Privacy Policy

The following Privacy Policy covers all the websites (“websites”) owned, affiliated or operated by Design You Trust. (“DYT”, “we”, “us”, “our”). It is our goal to bring you information tailored to your personal interests but, at the same time, protect your privacy. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy.

By visiting 101 Media Lab websites, submitting information or using any of our products and services, you are accepting the practiced outlined in this Privacy Policy.

This Privacy Policy covers DYT’s treatment of personal information that 101 Media Lab gathers when you are on our websites and when you are using DYT services. Also, this Privacy Policy covers DYT’s treatment of any personal information that DYT’s business partners share with us. This Privacy Policy does not cover information collected elsewhere, including without limitation offline and on sites linked to and from the website as well as the practices of third parties that DYT does not control or own, or individuals that DYT does not employ or manage.

In addition to reviewing this Privacy Policy, please read our User Agreement. Your use of our websites constitutes agreement to its terms and conditions as well.

This Privacy Policy may be modified from time to time so check back often. Continued access of our websites by you will constitute your acceptance of the changes or revisions to the Privacy Policy.

## Information You Provide to Us

The website generally collects personally identifying information with your specific knowledge and consent. This includes but is not limited to when you register for our forums, enter a sweepstakes and complete a survey. You can choose not to provide us with certain information, but you may not be able to take advantage of many of our special features such as posting on our forums. – Registration: In order to use select parts of our websites such as the forum, you must complete a registration form. As part of this registration forum, we require your email address and date of birth. Optional information such as your referrer or time zone may also be requested.

## Automatic Information

Our servers may automatically collect information about your computer when you visit our websites, including without limitation the website that referred you, your Internet Protocol (“IP”) and other usage and traffic information. DYT uses this statistical information to analyze trends, gather demographic information and administer our websites so we may provide improved web experiences to our readers. The information is not in a manner that would identify you personally. We may provide statistical information, not personal information, to our partners about how our users, collectively use our websites. We share this information to our partners, so that they may further understand the usage of their areas and our websites, so that they too could provide you with a better web experience. There may also be occasion when we are legally required to provide access to our database in order to cooperate with police investigations or other legal proceedings. In those instances, the information is provided only for that purpose.

## Cookies

Cookies are messages given to a web browser by a web server that are placed in storage. Their purpose is to identify users and possibly prepare customized WebPages for them. We may use cookies to control the display of ads, to track usage patterns on our websites, to deliver editorial content, and to record registration and personalization information. For example, if you register on any part of our websites and are given the option to save your user name and password on your computer, we can provide this convenience to you by placing a cookie on your computer. Our cookies may contain personally identifiable information and such cookies may be shared with our affiliates and other companies. DYT does not collection personal information, and we do not combined information collected through cookies with other personal information to tell us who you are or what your screen name or email address is. Some of our advertisers may occasionally service you cookies as well. We do not have control over cookies placed by advertisers. If you don’t want any cookies, your web browser likely includes an option that allows you to not accept them. However, if you set your browser to refused cookies, some portions of the website may not function properly.

## Sharing Information

We neither rent nor sell your personal information to anyone. We share your personal information only with your consent or to the entities described below: – Agents We employ other companies and people to perform tasks on our behalf and need to share your information with them to provide products or services to you. Examples include sending postal mail and email, removing repetitive information from customers’ lists, analyzing data, providing marketing assistant, and providing customer service. You hereby consent to our sharing of your personal information for the above purposes. – Business Transfers As our business changes and grow, we may buy or sell various assets. In the event all or a portion of the assets owned or controlled by DYT are sold, assigned, transferred or acquired by another company, the information from and about our website users may be among the transferred assets

## Children and Parents

Our websites are not meant for children, especially those under 13. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13. In the event that we learn that we have collected any personal information from a child under the age of 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information from our database as quickly as possible.

## Third Party Websites

DYT may permit you to link to other websites on the Internet, and other websites may contain links to the 101 Media Lab websites. These other websites are not under DYT control. The privacy and security practices of websites linked to or from the DYT are not covered by this Privacy Policy, and DYT is not responsible for the privacy or security practices or the content of such websites.
